**You Make a Difference!** Our mission and operations are funded entirely by Patriots like you! Please [support the 2024 Year-End Campaign](https://patriotpost.us/donation/new?utm_campaign=55&utm_content=precontent_6&utm_medium=web&utm_source=patriotpost.us) now.

Privacy Policy for _The Patriot Post_

=========================================

### Our Commitment to Privacy

Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us, and to assist you in making informed decisions when using The Patriot Post website. Unlike most websites, we have no advertising so there are no third party advertisers collecting marketing information about you. Regarding the small amount of information we do collect, we do not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third parties.

By using our web site, you are agreeing, without qualification or limitation, to be bound by this Privacy Policy. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, the terms "The Patriot Post" or “we” or "us" or "our" refers to Publius Press, Inc. The term "you" refers to the user or viewer of our website.

### Information Collection and Use

When you visit our website you may provide us with two types of information: (i) personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis (“Personal Information”), and (ii) website use information collected on an aggregate basis through a website statistics program as you and others browse our website (“Use Information”).

In summary, we collect and use data internally for these purposes:

* Enhance the functionality of the Website (certain messages or pages cannot be shown or suppressed unless cookies are enabled)
* Enhance the security of the Website (certain forms cannot be submitted unless cookies are enabled)
* Gather data about Website traffic and how users interact with Website content (analytics)

Certain third parties may collect some data:

* Google, for the purposes of gathering data about Website traffic and how users interact with Website content (analytics)

### Website Statistics Gathering

From time to time we collect certain Use Information from our servers that relates to the use of our website, including but not limited to Internet Protocol addresses, Internet domain names, the web browser and operating system used to access the website, the files visited, the time spent in each file, and the time and date of each visit. We use this information to improve our website, for example by enhancing pages or features that are visited frequently.

This website may place and access cookies when you visit the website. A cookie is a small data file that websites commonly write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file contains information that can identify you each time you visit the website. This website uses cookies as a way to measure activity and traffic patterns on the website. You may choose to set your computer to reject cookies if you desire.

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

Personal Information which you may provide to us through use of the website includes, without limitation, your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number, and other similar information. If you submit your Personal Information to us, it may be retained in our internal database system for data collection, business research and record keeping purposes.

From time to time our website may request additional information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose additional information that may be requested. Information requested via surveys and contests may include additional demographic information.

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages along with your email address and our responses in secured online and offline databases to help us develop and improve our business and to enhance your use of our website.

We use Personal Information for purposes of operating our website, administering our business activities and providing customer service. The Personal Information you provide to us when filling out and submitting an online form or requesting us to contact you will be used for the purpose for which it was provided – such as contacting you or processing a request. Occasionally, we may also use the Personal Information we collect to notify you about important changes to our website, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable.

We may also share your Personal Information with third parties under the following circumstances:

When you consent to disclosure;  
To enforce or apply The Patriot Post's agreements or protect The Patriot Post and its rights;  
By operation of law, when such Personal Information is transferred as a part of sale of assets including the assets represented by this website;  
In the event that The Patriot Post, or substantially all of its assets, are acquired outside of the ordinary course of business and such Personal Information may be one of the transferred assets;  
In connection with a subpoena or other judicial or governmental request for information; or  
In the event we use a credit card processing company to bill website visitors for products and services which they request.

In connection with your use of the website, you may choose to post or upload certain materials onto the website, including business information and contact information. You understand and agree that the information and materials you post on the website are capable of being viewed by the public and will not be protected under the terms of this Privacy Policy.

### Linked Sites

It is important to note that The Patriot Post's website contains links to other websites and that those other websites may not follow the same privacy policies as The Patriot Post. This includes links from advertisers, content providers and trade partners who may use our logo and/or style as part of a co-branding agreement. These other websites may collect data from you that The Patriot Post would not and may use that data in ways that The Patriot Post would not.

### E-mail Transmissions

When you send The Patriot Post an e-mail transmission, the e-mail transmission is not guaranteed to be secure. Accordingly, e-mail transmissions are not necessarily protected from unauthorized access. Transmission of information via e-mail is at your own risk.

### Application of Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to information collected by and through The Patriot Post's website. It does not apply to any other services of The Patriot Post or dealings with users or customers and does not apply to third party sites which may be linked to The Patriot Post website.

### Children and Privacy

The Patriot Post does not knowingly collect information from or about children age 13 and under. This website is not marketed towards children age 13 and under and is not intended to be used by them. If we find that we have collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will immediately delete that information.

### Correction/Updating of Personal Information

If your Personal Information changes (such as your telephone number or address), you can request that we modify such information by contacting us. We will comply with all appropriate requests within a reasonable time. In addition, you may also contact us to know what Personal Information we have collected from you or if you would like us to delete the Personal Information we have collected about you from our database.

### Security

The Patriot Post takes precautions to protect your Personal Information. Our safeguards include technical means and policies and procedures that our staff is trained to follow. If as a registered user you receive a password, you should keep it confidential because it is the key to access to the information held by The Patriot Post about you. If you leave your computer's internet browser running and someone else uses your computer, they will be able to access your account; thus, if your computer is not physically secure remember to shut down your browser before you leave it.

Our website uses Secure Socket Layers (SSL) to help protect the confidentiality of your check card or credit card information. As your order is transmitted to us, SSL technology helps prevent other parties from viewing or obtaining your card information.

Our website also uses a SSL protocol for all outgoing transmissions. SSL secretly encodes information that is being sent over the Internet, helping to ensure that the information remains confidential.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also take steps to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. The Patriot Post employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to help ensure our customers' information is protected.

Please note that while we try to reduce the likelihood of accidental disclosures and unintended access and modification of Personal Information, it is impossible to eliminate this possibility completely.

### Protecting Your Own Privacy

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information.

### Modifications to Our Privacy Policies

The Patriot Post reserves the right to change our privacy policies at any time, except as may be prohibited by law. If we decide to change our privacy policies and practices, we will post appropriate changes to this Privacy Policy on our website and we will revise the “Last Updated” date at the bottom of this document accordingly. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about our current policies relating to our collection, use and disclosure of your information. Use of our website after the Privacy Policy has changed means that you consent to the Privacy Policy as changed.

### Right to Opt Out

We give you the opportunity to elect not to receive future materials from us. You have the right to opt out of receiving materials via e-mail by unsubscribing/managing subscription preferences [here](https://patriotpost.us/subscription/login). Additionally, you have the right to opt out of receiving donor promotional items by mail when making a donation. This is an option in a drop-down box under donation information. If you sign up for an electronic newsletter or e-mail list, each message will include instructions on how to "unsubscribe" from that list.

### Contacting The Patriot Post

Our website provides a Contact Us section to facilitate feedback from site visitors. Please use this feature to notify us if you have any questions, concerns or complaints about the manner in which your Personal Information has been collected or handled by The Patriot Post, or contact The Patriot Post's offices at 820 Scenic Hwy., Lookout Mountain, TN 37350.

Last Updated: November 15, 2011.

### Memesters Union

### Cartoons

### Top Opinion

*      [Mark Alexander Trump Day 1: Demolish the Demos’ Rigged Midterm Election Strategy](https://patriotpost.us/alexander/112180-trump-day-1-demolish-the-demos-rigged-midterm-election-strategy-2024-11-20)
*      [Stephen Moore Breaking Up Google Will Be a Great American Catastrophe](https://patriotpost.us/opinion/112167-breaking-up-google-will-be-a-great-american-catastrophe-2024-11-20)
*      [Tim Graham TV Stars Mock the Tiny Threat of Trans Women in Sports](https://patriotpost.us/opinion/112166-tv-stars-mock-the-tiny-threat-of-trans-women-in-sports-2024-11-20)
*      [Star Parker Young, Black, Hispanic Americans Would Opt Out of Social Security Even if It Wasn’t Broken](https://patriotpost.us/opinion/112164-young-black-hispanic-americans-would-opt-out-of-social-security-even-if-it-wasnt-broken-2024-11-20)
*      [Byron York Schumer to GOP: Please Don’t Do What We Were Going to Do to You](https://patriotpost.us/opinion/112162-schumer-to-gop-please-dont-do-what-we-were-going-to-do-to-you-2024-11-20)
*      [Betsy McCaughey Kamala’s Defeat Ushers in New, Law-and-Order Future for Cities](https://patriotpost.us/opinion/112161-kamalas-defeat-ushers-in-new-law-and-order-future-for-cities-2024-11-20)
*      [Hans von Spakovsky Pennsylvania Officials Openly Admit to Trying to Steal Senate Seat](https://patriotpost.us/opinion/112158-pennsylvania-officials-openly-admit-to-trying-to-steal-senate-seat-2024-11-20)
*      [The Washington Stand Dems Continue Infighting Over Trans Issues After Election Loss](https://patriotpost.us/opinion/112160-dems-continue-infighting-over-trans-issues-after-election-loss-2024-11-20)
*      [The Babylon Bee Kamala Asks Biden to Stop Doing Trump Dance in Cabinet Meetings](https://patriotpost.us/opinion/112152-kamala-asks-biden-to-stop-doing-trump-dance-in-cabinet-meetings-2024-11-20)

[Wear Your Patriotism on Your Sleeve

Shop Now](https://patriotpostshop.com/)

### The Foundation

“The importance of piety and religion; of industry and frugality; of prudence, economy, regularity and an even government; all … are essential to the well-being of a family.” —Samuel Adams (1780)

#### Who We Are

The Patriot Post is a highly acclaimed weekday digest of news analysis, policy and opinion written from the heartland — as opposed to the MSM’s ubiquitous Beltway echo chambers — for grassroots leaders nationwide. [More](https://patriotpost.us/about)

#### What We Offer

#### On the Web

We provide solid conservative perspective on the most important issues, including analysis, opinion columns, headline summaries, memes, cartoons and much more.

#### Via Email

Choose our full-length Digest or our quick-reading Snapshot for a summary of important news. We also offer Cartoons & Memes on Monday and Alexander’s column on Wednesday.

#### Our Mission

The Patriot Post is steadfast in our mission to extend the [endowment of Liberty](https://patriotpost.us/alexander/3467) to the next generation by advocating for individual rights and responsibilities, supporting the restoration of constitutional limits on government and the judiciary, and promoting free enterprise, national defense and traditional American values. We are a rock-solid conservative touchstone for the expanding ranks of [grassroots Americans Patriots](https://patriotpost.us/alexander/9612) from all walks of life. Our [mission and operation budgets](https://patriotpost.us/about/budget) are **not financed** by any political or special interest groups, and to protect our editorial integrity, we **accept no advertising**. We are sustained solely by _you_. Please [support The Patriot Fund today](https://patriotpost.us/donation/new)!

The Patriot Post and [Patriot Foundation Trust](https://patriotfoundationtrust.org/), in keeping with our [Military Mission of Service](https://patriotpost.us/about/mission) to our uniformed service members and veterans, are proud to support and promote the [National Medal of Honor Heritage Center](https://www.mohhc.org/), the [Congressional Medal of Honor Society](https://www.cmohs.org/), both the [Honoring the Sacrifice](https://honoringthesacrifice.com/) and [Warrior Freedom Service Dogs](https://www.warriorfreedom.org/) aiding wounded veterans, the [Tunnel to Towers Foundation](https://t2t.org/), the [National Veterans Entrepreneurship Program](https://www.utc.edu/gary-w-rollins-college-of-business/outreach-programs/national-veterans-entrepreneurship-program), the [Folds of Honor](https://foldsofhonor.org/about-us/) outreach, and [Officer Christian Fellowship](https://www.ocfusa.org/), the [Air University Foundation](https://www.airuniversity.af.edu/), and [Naval War College Foundation](https://nwcfoundation.org/), and the [Naval Aviation Museum Foundation](https://www.navalaviationmuseum.org/). "Greater love has no one than this, to lay down one's life for his friends." (John 15:13)

##### Email Subscriptions

##### Support The Patriot Post

[FAQ](https://patriotpost.us/about/faq) / [Contact Us](https://patriotpost.us/contact) / [Terms of Use](https://patriotpost.us/about/terms) / [Privacy Policy](https://patriotpost.us/about/privacy) / [Reprinting Policy](https://patriotpost.us/about/terms#reprint)

★ PUBLIUS ★

“Our cause is noble; it is the cause of mankind!” —George Washington

Please join us in prayer for our nation — that righteous leaders would rise and prevail and we would be united as Americans. Pray also for the protection of our Military Patriots, Veterans, First Responders, and their families. Please lift up your Patriot team and our mission to support and defend our Republic's Founding Principle of Liberty, that the fires of freedom would be ignited in the hearts and minds of our countrymen.

The Patriot Post is protected speech, as enumerated in the [First Amendment](https://patriotpost.us/alexander/77001-the-systemic-redlining-of-free-speech-violating-civil-rights-2021-01-13) and enforced by the [Second Amendment](https://patriotpost.us/alexander/40303-the-first-civil-right-to-keep-and-bear-arms-2016-01-27) of the Constitution of the United States of America, in accordance with the [endowed](https://patriotpost.us/alexander/18968-the-endowed-rights-of-man-2013-07-03) and [unalienable Rights of All Mankind](https://patriotpost.us/alexander/33261-unalienable-rights-of-man-a-civics-lesson-2015-02-18).

Copyright © 2024 The Patriot Post. All Rights Reserved.

The Patriot Post does not support Internet Explorer. We recommend installing the latest version of [Microsoft Edge](https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/edge), [Mozilla Firefox](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/new/), or [Google Chrome](https://www.google.com/chrome/).
